Guide to the William Rose Benét Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1897-1955; 1922-1950; Series I; 22.43; 50 boxes
  - General Correspondence
    - Carleton, Sara King, 1947-1950, undated (Box 8, Folder 294)
    - Carman, Bliss, 1914 February 16 (Box 8, Folder 295)
    - Carmer, Carl, 1941–1950 (Box 8, Folder 296)
    - Carnovsky, Leon, 1948 July 3 (Box 8, Folder 297)
    - Carruth, Hayden, 1949 December 5 (Box 8, Folder 298)
    - Carse, Robert, 1929 April 10 (Box 8, Folder 299)
    - Carter, Thomas Henry, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 300)
    - Case, Edward Murray, 1949–1950 (Box 8, Folder 301)
    - Cate, Garth, 1949 June 21 (Box 8, Folder 302)
    - Cather, Willa (to Elinor Wylie), undated (Box 8, Folder 303)
    - Catholic Poetry Society of America, 1950 March (Box 8, Folder 304)
    - The Catholic World, 1950 March 22 (Box 8, Folder 305)
    - Cendrars, Blaise, [1922 January 18?] (Box 8, Folder 306)
    - Century Association (New York, N.Y.), 1930 April 3 (Box 8, Folder 307)
    - The Century Magazine, 1917–1918 (Box 8, Folder 308)
    - Chaffee, Eleanor Alletta, 1948–1950 (Box 8, Folder 309)
    - Chalmers, Harvey, 1947; 1949 (Box 8, Folder 310)
    - Chapin, Helen [Burwell?], 1936 June 27 (Box 8, Folder 311)
    - Chapin, Henry, 1934; 1943 (Box 8, Folder 312)
    - Chapin, Katherine Garrison, 1929-1949, undated (Box 8, Folder 313)
    - Chapman, Marion, 1923 January 7 (Box 9, Folder 314)
    - Charles H. Cleaves Agency, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 315)
    - Charles Scribner's Sons, 1909–1950 (Box 9, Folder 316)
    - Chicago Review, 1946–1947 (Box 9, Folder 317)
    - Child, Charles, undated (Box 9, Folder 318)
    - Children's Aid Society (New York, N.Y.), 1944–1950 (Box 9, Folder 319)
    - Children's World Theatre, 1949–1950 (Box 9, Folder 320)
    - Chilton, Eleanor Carroll, 1928-1930, undated (Box 9, Folder 321)
    - Chimera, 1944–1945 (Box 9, Folder 322)
    - Choate School, 1925–1926 (Box 9, Folder 323)
    - The Chocorua Press, undated (Box 9, Folder 324)
    - Christensen, Francis, 1949 January 15 (Box 9, Folder 325)
    - Christian Science Monitor, 1943 October 15 (Box 9, Folder 326)
    - Christmas cards, undated (Box 9, Folder 327)
    - Chubb, Edwin Watts, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 328)
    - Chubb, Thomas Caldecot, 1933-1950, undated (Box 9, Folder 329)
    - Church, William Howard, 1940-1947, undated (Box 9, Folder 330-331)
    - The Churchman, 1941–1949 (Box 9, Folder 332)
    - Chworowsky, Karl M., 1947–1948 (Box 9, Folder 333)
    - Ciardi, John, 1947; 1950 (Box 9, Folder 334)
    - Ciofalo, Joanne, 1948-1949, undated (Box 9, Folder 335)
    - Citizens' Housing Council of New York, 1947 February (Box 9, Folder 336)
    - Clapp, Frederick Mortimer, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 337)
    - Clark, Charles Upson, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 338)
    - Clark, Donald L[emen?], 1942; 1949 (Box 9, Folder 339)
    - Clark, Marguerite, 1929 January 8 (Box 9, Folder 340)
    - Clark, Marie Whitback, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 341)
    - Clarke, George Herbert, 1942 October 7 (Box 9, Folder 342)
    - Clarke, Henriette, 1948–1949 (Box 9, Folder 343)
    - Classmate, 1944 January 3 (Box 9, Folder 344)
    - Clayburgh, Alma, 1950 May 8 (Box 9, Folder 345)
    - Clayton, Gertrude, 1938–1950 (Box 9, Folder 346)
    - Clemens, Cyril, 1944-1950, undated (Box 9, Folder 347)
    - Clough, Ruth Crary, 1948-1950, undated (Box 9, Folder 348)
    - Clyne, Sara, 1948–1950 (Box 9, Folder 349)
    - Coats, Nellie M. (Nellie Mae), undated (Box 9, Folder 350)
    - Coatsworth, Elizabeth Jane, 1942-1950, undated (Box 9, Folder 351)
    - Coe, Arthur, 1949 November (Box 9, Folder 352)
    - Coe, Lloyd; Coe, Ed, 1947; 1950 (Box 9, Folder 353)
    - Coffee, John M[ain], 1944 October 3 (Box 9, Folder 354)
    - Coffin, Robert P. Tristan (Robert Peter Tristan), 1937-1950, undated (Box 9, Folder 355)
    - Cohn, Nathan, 1949–1950 (Box 9, Folder 356)
    - Coker, Adelaide, 1946–1950 (Box 9, Folder 357)
    - Colamussi, Fabrizio, 1948–1949 (Box 10, Folder 358)
    - Colby, Fanny, 1942-1950, undated (Box 10, Folder 359)
    - Colby, Nathalie Sedgwick, undated (Box 10, Folder 360)
    - Colefax, Sibyl, 1927, undated (Box 10, Folder 361)
    - Coleman, McAlister, 1950 February 24 (Box 10, Folder 362)
    - Coleman, Marion Moore, 1943 December 30 (Box 10, Folder 363)
    - Coll, Blanche O., 1947 March (Box 10, Folder 364)
    - College Poetry Society of America, 1939 January 17 (Box 10, Folder 365)
    - Collins, Seward, 1928 December 17 (Box 10, Folder 366)
    - Colony, [Horatio?], [?] March 30 (Box 10, Folder 367)
    - Colton, Amy Richards, 1944-1949, undated (Box 10, Folder 368)
    - Colum, Padraic, 1922-1950, undated (Box 10, Folder 369)
    - Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc., 1938; 1947 (Box 10, Folder 370)
    - Columbia University, 1938–1949 (Box 10, Folder 371)
    - Columbia University. Teachers College, 1949 May (Box 10, Folder 372)
    - Combes, Gladys Ewing, 1946 May (Box 10, Folder 373)
    - Cominsky, Jack
    - Committee on Cathedral Relations with Latin America, 1943 September 23 (Box 10, Folder 374)
    - Common Ground, 1942–1943 (Box 10, Folder 375)
    - Community Service Society of New York, 1946; 1950 (Box 10, Folder 376)
    - Conant, Isabel Fiske, 1943, undated (Box 10, Folder 377)
    - Condé Nast Publications, 1947 May 21 (Box 10, Folder 378)
    - Condolence letters, 1943-1950, undated (Box 10, Folder 379)
    - Conference on the Scientific Spirit and Democratic Faith, 1949–1950 (Box 10, Folder 380)
    - Conkling, Grace Hazard, 1914-1929, undated (Box 10, Folder 381)
    - Connolly, Terence L. (Terence Leo), 1948 July (Box 10, Folder 382)
    - Converse, Florence, 1943-1950, undated (Box 10, Folder 383)
    - Cooper, Alice C[ecilia], 1944; 1948 (Box 10, Folder 384)
    - Cooper, "Billy", 1949 (Box 10, Folder 385)
    - Cooper, Charles W. (Charles William), 1945 August 12 (Box 10, Folder 386)
    - Cooper Union for the Advancement of Science and Art, 1943 September (Box 10, Folder 387)
    - Copland, Aaron, 1950 February 26 (Box 10, Folder 388)
    - Corliss Bros. Incorporated, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 389)
    - Cornell, Katharine, 1935 October 30 (Box 10, Folder 390)
    - Corning, Howard McKinley, 1948 February (Box 10, Folder 391)
    - Cory, Robert, 1950 March (Box 10, Folder 392)
    - Coudert Brothers, 1903-1931, undated (Box 10, Folder 393-396)
    - Council Against Intolerance in America, 1949 September 27 (Box 10, Folder 397)
    - Council for Pan American Democracy, 1943 August 2 (Box 10, Folder 398)
    - Council on Books in Wartime, 1942–1943 (Box 10, Folder 399)
    - Counterattack, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 400)
    - Cousins, Norman
    - Coward-McCann, Inc., 1928-1949, undated (Box 11, Folder 401)
    - Cowden, Roy William, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 402)
    - Cowley-Brown, John Stapleton, 1946-1949, undated (Box 11, Folder 403)
    - Coyle, Kathleen, undated (Box 11, Folder 404)
    - Cram, Mildred, 1948-1950, undated (Box 11, Folder 405)
    - Crane, Nathalia, 1924-1935, undated (Box 11, Folder 406)
    - Creekmore, Hubert, 1948 August 27 (Box 11, Folder 407)
    - Creel, George, 1949 February (Box 11, Folder 408)
    - Cring, M. R., 1947-1948, undated (Box 11, Folder 409)
    - Crosby, Raymond Moreau, 1929-1944, undated (Box 11, Folder 410)
    - Cross, Wilbur L. (Wilbur Lucius), 1947 December 26 (Box 11, Folder 411)
    - Crowninshield, Frank, 1923–1946 (Box 11, Folder 412)
    - Cullum, Winifred, 1949 April (Box 11, Folder 413)
    - Cummings, E. E. (Edward Estlin), 1933, undated (Box 11, Folder 414)
    - Cummington Press, 1946 December (Box 11, Folder 415)
    - Cummins, Virginia Kent, 1949 December 21 (Box 11, Folder 416)
    - Cuppy, Will, undated (Box 11, Folder 417)
    - Curl, Barbara, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 418)
    - Curnow, Allen, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 419)
    - Curry, Helen, 1948 June (Box 11, Folder 420)
    - Curtis, Christine Turner, 1944-1950, undated (Box 11, Folder 421)
    - Curtis Publishing Company, 1939 October 19 (Box 11, Folder 422)
    - Curtler, Martin S., 1947–1948 (Box 11, Folder 423)
    - "D" general, 1928-1950, undated (Box 11, Folder 424-426)
    - Da Boll, Raymond F., 1950 May 19 (Box 11, Folder 427)
    - Daiches, David, 1948–1950 (Box 11, Folder 428)
    - Dalton, Power, 1950 March 10 (Box 11, Folder 429)
    - Dalven, Rae, 1945–1949 (Box 11, Folder 430-431)
    - Dalven, Rae, 1949-1950, undated (Box 12, Folder 432-433)
    - Clippings removed from Dalven, Rae, 1949 (Box 114 (Oversize), Folder 3324)
    - Daly, Jim, 1942–1943 (Box 12, Folder 434)
    - Damon, S. Foster (Samuel Foster), 1936–1948 (Box 12, Folder 435)
    - Damrosch, Walter, undated (Box 12, Folder 436)
    - Dan Golenpaul Associates, 1943 September 21 (Box 12, Folder 437)
    - Danner, Sara Kolb, 1938-1950, undated (Box 12, Folder 438)
    - Darcy, Louise, 1949-1950, undated (Box 12, Folder 439)
    - Darling, Helen, 1943; 1945 (Box 12, Folder 440)
    - Darnbacher, F., 1949 (Box 12, Folder 441)
    - Davenport, Basil, 1942-1950, undated (Box 12, Folder 442)
    - Davidman, Joy, 1939-1949, undated (Box 12, Folder 443)
    - Clipping removed from Davidman, Joy, 1949 November 9 (Box 114 (Oversize), Folder 3325)
    - Davidson, Gustav, 1947-1950, undated (Box 12, Folder 444-445)
    - Davidson, Harold G. (Harold Gibson), 1949 (Box 12, Folder 446)
    - Davidson, Jo, 1946, undated (Box 12, Folder 447)
    - Davies, Mary Carolyn, 1928 December 18 (Box 12, Folder 448)
    - Davis, Curtis Carroll, 1950 March (Box 12, Folder 449)
    - Davis, Elmer [Holmes?], 1939 July 8 (Box 12, Folder 450)
    - Davis, Frank Marshall, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 451)
    - Davis, Hussoldt, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 452)
    - Davis, Malcolm W. (Malcolm Waters), 1928 April 6 (Box 12, Folder 453)
    - Davis, Mary Gould, 1949–1950 (Box 12, Folder 454)
    - Davis, Robert Gorham, 1948–1949 (Box 12, Folder 455)
    - Deane, Martha, 1948 November 10 (Box 12, Folder 456)
    - De Banke, Cécile, 1943-1948, undated (Box 12, Folder 457)
    - De Bosis, Lauro, 1929, undated (Box 12, Folder 458)
    - De Castro, Adolphe [Denzinger?], 1949 December 21 (Box 12, Folder 459)
    - Decker, Clarence R[aymond?], 1947; 1949 (Box 12, Folder 460)
    - Decker Press, 1948-1950, undated (Box 12, Folder 461)
    - De Ford, Miriam Allen, 1948–1950 (Box 12, Folder 462)
    - De Kay, Drake, 1937-1950, undated (Box 12, Folder 463)
    - Delafield, Eugene L., 1944-1950, undated (Box 12, Folder 464-465)
    - De La Mare, Walter, 1922-1947, undated (Box 12, Folder 466)
    - Delano, William Adams, 1949–1950 (Box 12, Folder 467)
    - De Lima, Agnes, 1948-1950, undated (Box 13, Folder 468)
    - Dell, Floyd, 1927–1928 (Box 13, Folder 469)
    - De Milk, Anna George, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 470)
    - Denning, Frances Kramer, 1950 January (Box 13, Folder 471)
    - Dent, Mary V., 1926-1929, undated (Box 13, Folder 472-473)
    - Derleth, August William, 1942–1949 (Box 13, Folder 474)
    - Dessart, Alice, 1948–1949 (Box 13, Folder 475)
    - Detroit Free Press, 1949 April (Box 13, Folder 476)
    - Detroit Public Library, 1945 April (Box 13, Folder 477)
    - Deutsch, Babette, 1923-1950, undated (Box 13, Folder 478)
    - De Villiers, Rudolphe Roesler, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 479)
    - Dewhurst, S. H., 1948 (Box 13, Folder 480)
    - De Witt, Samuel A., 1943–1944 (Box 13, Folder 481)
    - Dickinson College, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 482)
    - Dillaway, Newton, 1949 June 14 (Box 13, Folder 483)
    - Dobie, J. Frank (James Frank), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 484)
    - Docili, Peter, 1950 March 30 (Box 13, Folder 485)
    - Dodd, Lee Wilson, 1929 January 3 (Box 13, Folder 486)
    - Dodd, Mead Company, 1934-1950, undated (Box 13, Folder 487)
    - Dodge, Dorothy, 1947 May (Box 13, Folder 488)
    - Donnan, Elizabeth, 1948 June 14 (Box 13, Folder 489)
    - Doro, Edward, 1943-1945, undated (Box 13, Folder 490)
    - Dos Passos, John, 1923-1950, undated (Box 13, Folder 491)
    - Doubleday, Doran Company, 1922-1950, undated (Box 13, Folder 492)
    - Douglas, Gilean, 1949–1950 (Box 13, Folder 493)
    - Downey, Fairfax, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 494)
    - Downing, Robert, 1945 February 14 (Box 13, Folder 495)
    - Downs, Elizabeth [C. (Elizabeth Crooks)?], 1926, undated (Box 13, Folder 496)
    - Drake, Leah Bodine, 1948-1950, undated (Box 13, Folder 497)
    - Dransfield, Jane, 1941; 1948 (Box 13, Folder 498)
    - Dreier, Thomas, 1947 September 23 (Box 13, Folder 499)
    - Drew, Fraser [Bragg?], 1950 (Box 13, Folder 500)
    - Drinkwater, John, 1924 June 28 (Box 13, Folder 501)
    - Drury, Francis K. W. (Francis Keese Wynkoop), 1950 January (Box 13, Folder 502)
    - Dryden, Brigida, 1930-1947, undated (Box 13, Folder 503-504)
    - Dryden Press, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 505)
    - Duell, Sloan & Pearce, 1942; 1945 (Box 13, Folder 506)
    - Duffield & Green, 1929-1934, undated (Box 13, Folder 507)
    - Dunbar, Virginia Esterly, 1946; 1949 (Box 13, Folder 508)
    - Duncan, Hazel, 1949–1950 (Box 13, Folder 509)
    - Dunlap, Katharine, 1939-1950, undated (Box 13, Folder 510)
    - Dunsany, Edward John Moreton Drax Plunkett, Baron, 1920; 1922 (Box 13, Folder 511)
    - Durant, Kenneth, 1945–1949 (Box 14, Folder 512)
    - Duryee, Mary Ballard, 1947-1948, undated (Box 14, Folder 513)
    - Dwiggins, W. A. (William Addison), 1915-1947, undated (Box 14, Folder 514)
    - "E" general, 1929-1950, undated (Box 14, Folder 515)
    - E.P. Dutton (Firm), 1943–1946 (Box 14, Folder 516)
    - Earle, Ferdinand, 1949–1950 (Box 14, Folder 517)
    - Earle, Olive, 1922 September 9 (Box 14, Folder 518)
    - Earls, Michael, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 519)
    - Eaton, Charles Edward, 1944–1950 (Box 14, Folder 520)
    - Eaton, Dorothy Burnham, 1948–1950 (Box 14, Folder 521)
    - Eberhart, Richard, 1949–1950 (Box 14, Folder 522)
    - Eberhart, W. Perry, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 523)
    - Eckhardt, Win, 1948-1950, undated (Box 14, Folder 524)
    - Eden, Helen Parry, 1914-1948, undated (Box 14, Folder 525)
    - Edson, C. L. (Charles Leroy), 1935-1948, undated (Box 14, Folder 526)
    - Edward, Donald Earl, 1949, undated (Box 14, Folder 527)
    - Eldridge, Paul, 1934 February 17 (Box 14, Folder 528)
    - Eliot, T. S. (Thomas Stearns), 1933 February 14 (Box 14, Folder 529)
    - [Ellerbe?] Paul, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 530)
    - Elliot, Jean (to Marjorie Flack), 1950 May 9 (Box 14, Folder 531)
    - Ellis, Carolyn, 1948–1950 (Box 14, Folder 532)
    - Ellis, Genevieve, 1944–1948 (Box 14, Folder 533)
    - Elton, William [R.?], 1948 September 24 (Box 14, Folder 534)
    - Emans, Elaine V., 1948 (Box 14, Folder 535)
    - Emanuel, Nan, 1948–1949 (Box 14, Folder 536)
    - Emanuel, V. R. [(Victor Rousseau)?], 1940 October 5 (Box 14, Folder 537)
    - Embury, Aymar, 1947 April 24 (Box 14, Folder 538)
    - Emory, William Closson, 1934 February 23 (Box 14, Folder 539)
    - Encore, 1942 July 21 (Box 14, Folder 540)
    - English-Speaking Union, 1930 March 14 (Box 14, Folder 541)
    - English-Speaking Union of the United States, 1927 October 24 (Box 14, Folder 542)
    - Epstein, Bennett, 1949–1950 (Box 14, Folder 543)
    - Eskew, Garnett L[aidlaw], 1948 (Box 14, Folder 544)
    - Essipoff, Marie Armstrong, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 545)
    - Evans, Ernestine, 1948 August (Box 14, Folder 546)
    - Evans, Florence Wilkinson, 1930-1949, undated (Box 14, Folder 547)
    - Everts, William, 1944–1950 (Box 14, Folder 548)
    - Exposition Press, 1948 September 24 (Box 14, Folder 549)
    - Eyre Spottis Woode, 1949–1950 (Box 14, Folder 550)
    - "F" general, 1909-1950, undated (Box 15, Folder 551-553)
    - F.E. Compton Company, 1946 May (Box 15, Folder 554)
    - Faber and Faber, 1930; 1932 (Box 15, Folder 555)
    - Factotum, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 556)
    - Famous Fantastic Mysteries, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 557)
    - Fandel, John, 1948 May 20 (Box 15, Folder 558)
    - Farma, William J[oseph], 1934–1935 (Box 15, Folder 559)
    - Farrar & Rinehart, 1942–1945 (Box 15, Folder 560)
    - Farrar, Straus, and Company, 1946-1950, undated (Box 15, Folder 561)
    - Farrell, James T. (James Thomas), 1950 January 7 (Box 15, Folder 562)
    - Fast, Howard, 1949 May 23 (Box 15, Folder 563)
    - Fatherless Children of France (Organization), 1920 December 6 (Box 15, Folder 564)
    - Favill, John, 1942 May 11 (Box 15, Folder 565)
    - Fechet, d'Alany, 1942-1950, undated (Box 15, Folder 566)
    - Fechet, Marie, 1906-1909, undated (Box 15, Folder 567)
    - Feipel, Louis N[icholas] (to Elinor Wylie), 1926 January 25 (Box 15, Folder 568)
    - Few, W. P. (William Preston), Mrs., 1949 May (Box 15, Folder 569)
    - Ficke, Arthur Davison; Ficke, Gladys, 1926-1949, undated (Box 15, Folder 570)
    - Copy of "Nannie and Warren: An American Ballad" removed from Ficke, Arthur Davison, undated (Box 114 (Oversize), Folder 3326)
    - Field, Sara Bard; Wood, Charles Eskine Scott, 1928–1941 (Box 15, Folder 571-575)
    - Field, Sara Bard; Wood, Charles Eskine Scott, 1941-1950, undated (Box 16, Folder 576-579)
    - Filler, Louis, 1947 February (Box 16, Folder 580)
    - Films in Review, 1950 January 26 (Box 16, Folder 581)
    - Firestone, Clark B. (Clark Barnaby), 1949 September (Box 16, Folder 582)
    - Firley, Henry J., 1946-1950, undated (Box 16, Folder 583)
    - Fisher, A. Hugh (Alfred Hugh), 1914-1939, undated (Box 16, Folder 584-585)
    - Fitch, Clyde, undated (Box 16, Folder 586)
    - Fitts, Dudley, 1939-1950, undated (Box 16, Folder 587-588)
    - Fitzgerald, Roy G. (Roy Gerald), 1947 May (Box 16, Folder 589)
    - Flaccus, Kimball, 1933–1941 (Box 16, Folder 590)
    - Flammonde, Paris, 1947; 1949 (Box 16, Folder 591)
    - Flanner, Hildegarde, 1925–1932 (Box 16, Folder 592)
    - Flaumenhaft, A. S., 1949–1950 (Box 16, Folder 593)
    - Fletcher, John Gould, 1933–1945 (Box 16, Folder 594)
    - Foley, John L., 1944 (Box 16, Folder 595)
    - Ford, Edsel, 1949 January (Box 16, Folder 596)
    - Ford, Ford Madox (to Elinor Wylie), 1927 June 2 (Box 16, Folder 597)
    - Forteen Society, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 598)
    - The Forum, 1909 June 24 (Box 16, Folder 599)
    - Foster, Marguerite Stevens, 1949–1950 (Box 16, Folder 600)
    - Foston, H., 1948 (Box 16, Folder 601)
    - Fowler, J. Beresford, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 602)
    - Fox, Janet E., 1949 May (Box 16, Folder 603)
    - Franchere, Hoyt C., 1950 March (Box 16, Folder 604)
    - Francis, Priscilla, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 605)
    - Francis, Robert, 1937 April 2 (Box 16, Folder 606)
    - Frank, Maude Morrison, 1946; 1949 (Box 17, Folder 607)
    - The Frank A. Munsey Company, 1918 (Box 17, Folder 608)
    - Frank McCaffrey Publishers, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 609)
    - Frankenberg, Lloyd, 1940-1950, undated (Box 17, Folder 610)
    - Frederick A. Stokes Company, 1909 (Box 17, Folder 611)
    - Free World, 1942 January 29 (Box 17, Folder 612)
    - Freedom House (U.S.), 1948 March (Box 17, Folder 613)
    - Freeland League, 1945 January (Box 17, Folder 614)
    - Freeman, Douglas Southall, 1946 May (Box 17, Folder 615)
    - Freeman, R. Austin (Richard Austin), [?] December 31 (Box 17, Folder 616)
    - Freitag, George H., 1946-1949, undated (Box 17, Folder 617)
    - Friede, Donald, undated (Box 17, Folder 618)
    - Friedman, Philip Allan, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 619)
    - Friends of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 620)
    - Frontier Films (New York, N.Y.), 1942 January 27 (Box 17, Folder 621)
    - Frost, Elizabeth Hollister, 1931; 1946 (Box 17, Folder 622)
    - Frost, Frances, 1931-1950, undated (Box 17, Folder 623)
    - Frost, Robert, 1933; 1949 (Box 17, Folder 624)
    - Frye, Burton C., 1950 (Box 17, Folder 625)
    - "G" general, 1926-19[53?], undated (Box 17, Folder 626-628)
    - G. C. Merriam Company, 1942–1949 (Box 17, Folder 629)
    - Gaffney, Wilbur G., 1949 October (Box 17, Folder 630)
    - Gahr, David, 1949 December (Box 17, Folder 631)
    - Galbraith, Georgie Starbuck, 1946-1950, undated (Box 17, Folder 632)
    - Gale, M. M., 1948 (Box 17, Folder 633)
    - Gale, Zona, 1922–1929 (Box 17, Folder 634)
    - Gannett, Lewis, 1950 May 10 (Box 17, Folder 635)
    - Garnett, Porter, 1949, undated (Box 17, Folder 636)
    - Garrett, Florence Rome, 1948–1949 (Box 17, Folder 637)
    - Gatewood, Richard D[uncan?], 1928 (Box 17, Folder 638)
    - Gauss, Christian, 1929 February 25 (Box 17, Folder 639)
    - Gaylord, Harriet, 1943, undated (Box 17, Folder 640)
    - Gelber, Lilienthal, Inc., 1941 January 6 (Box 17, Folder 641)
    - George, Carrie M., 1945; 1949 (Box 17, Folder 642)
    - George G. Harrap Co., 1945–1949 (Box 17, Folder 643)
    - Georges, Joel S[amuel], 1950 (Box 17, Folder 644)
    - Georgia State Library, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 645)
    - Gephart, Besse P[atterson], 1945–1949 (Box 17, Folder 646)
    - Gerry, Helen, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 647)
    - Geruso, Hallett, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 648)
    - Ghiselin, Brewster, 1950 May 6 (Box 18, Folder 649)
    - Gidlow, Elsa, 1938, undated (Box 18, Folder 650)
    - Gidney, James B., 1948 July 2 (Box 18, Folder 651)
    - Gilbert, Rodney, 1947 December (Box 18, Folder 652)
    - Gilbert, Warren, 1927–1928 (Box 18, Folder 653)
    - Gilder, Rodman, 1943; 1948 (Box 18, Folder 654)
    - Gilkyson, Phoebe H., 1944 (Box 18, Folder 655)
    - Gill, D[aisy] Sanial, 1943, undated (Box 18, Folder 656)
    - Gillis, Adolph, 1935; 1948 (Box 18, Folder 657)
    - Gillman, Richard, 1947-1950, undated (Box 18, Folder 658)
    - Gillmore, Inez Hayes, 1927-1950, undated (Box 18, Folder 659)
    - Ginn and Company, 1933; 1945 (Box 18, Folder 660)
    - Ginsberg, Louis, 1948–1950 (Box 18, Folder 661)
    - Giordan, Alma Roberts, 1949–1950 (Box 18, Folder 662)
    - Glaenzer, Richard Butler, 1915; 1933 (Box 18, Folder 663)
    - Glaze, Andrew, 1948 July 2 (Box 18, Folder 664)
    - Gleason, George Scott, 1928 December 19 (Box 18, Folder 665)
    - Glines, Ellen Barbour (to Elinor Wylie), [?] February 12 (Box 18, Folder 666)
    - The Globe and Mail, 1949 February (Box 18, Folder 667)
    - Goddard, Gloria, 1929 January 8 (Box 18, Folder 668)
    - Gode, Alexander, 1948 November (Box 18, Folder 669)
    - Goff, Charles Weer (to Elinor Wylie), 1928 March 22 (Box 18, Folder 670)
    - Golas, Tad, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 671)
    - Gomme, Geoffrey, 1928-1947, undated (Box 18, Folder 672)
    - Goodfellow, Dorothy, 1948–1950 (Box 18, Folder 673)
    - Goodman, Mae Winkler, 1947–1950 (Box 18, Folder 674)
    - Goodman, Ryah Tumarkin, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 675)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop (Boston, Mass.), 1945 November 8 (Box 18, Folder 676)
    - Gordon, Don, 1946–1950 (Box 18, Folder 677)
    - Gorman, Herbert Sherman, 1922, undated (Box 18, Folder 678)
    - Goski, John, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 679)
    - Gotham Book Mart, 1941-1948, undated (Box 18, Folder 680)
    - Gouge, Lucille, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 681)
    - Grahame, Roberta Margaret, 1950 January (Box 18, Folder 682)
    - Gramercy Boys' Club, 1942–1950 (Box 18, Folder 683)
    - Grandy, Julia Selden, 1943–1949 (Box 18, Folder 684)
    - Granger, Mary, 1942-1949, undated (Box 18, Folder 685)
    - Grant, Gladys Edgerton, 1949–1950 (Box 18, Folder 686)
    - Grant, Paul S., undated (Box 18, Folder 687)
    - Graves, Robert, undated (Box 18, Folder 688)
    - Grebanier, Bernard D. N., 1945, undated (Box 18, Folder 689)
    - Green, Julia Boynton, 1945–1950 (Box 18, Folder 690)
    - Green, Paul, 1944 January 10 (Box 18, Folder 691)
    - Greene, Ward, 1942-1944, undated (Box 18, Folder 692)
    - Printed version of poem, "Decoration Day," removed from Greene, Ward, 1944 (Box 114 (Oversize), Folder 3327)
    - Greenfield, Louis, 1949-1950, undated (Box 18, Folder 693)
    - Greenwich Village Historical Society, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 694)
    - Gregory, Alyse, 1926-1949, undated (Box 18, Folder 695)
    - Gregory, Horace, 1933-1950, undated (Box 19, Folder 696)
    - Greif, Amy [F?], 1948 (Box 19, Folder 697)
    - Grey, Pamela, 19[12?] August 12 (Box 19, Folder 698)